Hey there, I wanted to show you a new feature which is cache
holdings in manual portfolios.
You can now add a theoretical cache value in your manual
portfolio, which is helpful to
more closely illustrate the balance of your manual portfolio.
This cache balance will be displayed and added to your all
holdings in all portfolio
balances too.
So to add a cache balance, what we want to do is click on edit
portfolio, and then we'll
click at the bottom, edit lots.
And at the bottom of this edit lots worksheet, there is a box to
add cache balance in portfolio.
I'm going to go ahead and add a value and hit save.
And once I hit save, you can see that the cache value is at the
bottom of my holdings tab,
and it even calculates the weight of the cache in my portfolio
too.
So the weight is updated as well as the overall balance of my
portfolio to reflect the cache
that I entered.
And as I said, this balance will also be added to your all
portfolios in all holdings pages.
So if we go to all holdings, we'll see all of our portfolios in
the holdings on one page.
If we scroll down to the bottom, we'll see cache, and if we
expand the row, we'll see
that there's cache in my income portfolio and my second
portfolio, and the corresponding
weights to each one of those cache balances with my overall
weights of all my holdings.
I can also update the cache in my portfolio when I'm adding new
tickers to my portfolio.
So if I also click on the add symbol button and I find a ticker
and I hit next, I'll
be able to add in a number of shares, a date of purchase, and a
cost for the new ticker
in my portfolio, which I'll do.
And I can edit the cache balance on this modal as well and hit
save, and my cache
balance will be updated there as well.
So this is a new feature which is cache holdings in manual
portfolios that lets you add a
theoretical cache value to more closely illustrate the balance of
your manual portfolios.
Thanks so much.